const question1 = [
  {
    "question": 'What was the year the first episode of The Simpsons aired?',
    "answer1": '1989',
    "answer2": '1987',
    "answer3": '1990',
    "answer4": '1986',
    "correct": '1989'
  },
  {
    "question": 'Homer was part of a barbershop quartet. what was it called?',
    "answer1": 'The Be Sharps',
    "answer2": 'The Ce sharps',
    "answer3": 'The De sharps',
    "answer4": 'The Ee sharps',
    "correct": 'The Be Sharps'
  },
  {
    "question": 'Who performed the role of Sideshow Bob in "The Simpsons" and was a former "Cheers" star?',
    "answer1": 'Ted Danson',
    "answer2": 'Kelsey Grammar',
    "answer3": 'Woody Harreison',
    "answer4": 'George Wendt',
    "correct": 'Kelsey Grammar'
  },
  {
    "question": 'What are Marges twin sisters called?',
    "answer1": 'Maggie & Sheila',
    "answer2": 'Tia & Tamera',
    "answer3": 'Patty & Selma',
    "answer4": 'Kristina & Karissa',
    "correct": 'Patty & Selma'
  },

  {
    "question": 'How many kids do Apu and Manjula have',
    "answer1": '6',
    "answer2": '7',
    "answer3": '8',
    "answer4": '9',
    "correct": '8'
  },

  {
    "question": 'What is Marges maiden name?',
    "answer1": 'Garnier',
    "answer2": 'Fitzgerald',
    "answer3": 'Never Revealed',
    "answer4": 'Bouvier',
    "correct": 'Bouvier'
  },

  {
    "question": 'What is Homers full time job?',
    "answer1": 'Duffman',
    "answer2": 'Chief of Police',
    "answer3": 'Nuclear Safety Inpector',
    "answer4": 'Bus Driver',
    "correct": 'Nuclear Safety Inpector'
  },

  {
    "question": 'What is Marges natural hair colour?',
    "answer1": 'Grey',
    "answer2": 'Blue',
    "answer3": 'Blonde',
    "answer4": 'Brown',
    "correct": 'Grey'
  },

  {
    "question": 'Which cartoon was the inspiration for The Itchy & Scratchy Show?',
    "answer1": 'Scooby Doo',
    "answer2": 'Bugs Bunny',
    "answer3": 'Tom & Jerry',
    "answer4": 'Danger Mouse',
    "correct": 'Tom & Jerry'
  },

  {
    "question": 'Whats the name of the Simpsons pet dog?',
    "answer1": 'Ruby',
    "answer2": 'Ralph',
    "answer3": 'Santas Little Helper',
    "answer4": 'Snowy',
    "correct": 'Santas Little Helper'
  },
];